Looks good.
Hmm?
Would you like some of that delicious sauce? It's probably the best sauce I've ever tasted.
Yummy.
You want to do that thing where you say you want to step on it later?
I'd love to.
Okay.
Aoi, if I don't do it, will you quit?
I'm in.
I'll give you my ass.
Okay.
Hello everyone. I'm Hiyori Hamagishi from Hinatazaka46.
Tomorrow we have a tour in Fukuoka, but I'm going to Fukuoka ahead of everyone else.
I'm going to eat my favorite, favorite gyoza now.
I'm going to eat gyoza.
I like meaty and juicy gyoza, and I love crispy ones.
Looking forward to it. I want to eat it soon.
It's fun to talk alone.
This time, I'm going to have....
It's an excellent kakata gyoza.
I'm nervous.
Thank you very much.
I'm in, I'm in.
What shall I order?
It's a big board.
I don't know what to order.
Oh, look. This is all alcohol.
Oh, I was wrong. It's this way.
It's this way. There are so many.
I'd like to hear what you recommend today. I'd like to ask you what you'd like to do today.
May I?
Let's see...
The oriental dumplings.
The meat.
The least amount of beef.
What do you recommend today?
Gomaba saba (mackerel), grilled beef, ginkgo nut, garland chrysanthemum oshikashi (rice with garland chrysanthemum)
I'd like to try the sesame mackerel.
Oolong tea for drinks, please.
Thank you very much.
Oolong tea with konabe sour.
I can order.
Yes, please.
Today, we're going to go to Uta's.
My glasses are so vast.
I'm back every once in a while.
This time...
It's my birthday.
I've come back to see you.
So last month.
Last month.
I'm here to see how it goes.
I'm looking forward to it.
Shall we go home?
Here we are.
This looks so good.
Looks delicious!
Sesame soba noodles.
Looks so good!Looks amazingly delicious!
I love sesame soba!
Bon appétit!
Yum!
Delicious!
It's so good!
Oh, my God.
Yummy, yummy, yummy.
The third one.
Oh, my gosh!
Here it comes.
Yummy.
Wow, it looks really good!
I can't wait to try it.
It's so good!
We'll be waiting for you.
Thank you for watching!
Thank you for dinner.
Yum! Delicious!
It's so good!
The type of chutan I like.
With this crispy texture
It's so good!
Oh, did they have some kind of spicy miso bark?
Spicy miso means...
It's gonna be like...
Yes! Yum!
Delicious!Delicious!
Delicious!
It's so good at karaoke!
What am I going to do?
I'm going to a concert tomorrow.
I don't know if it's okay to eat something like this.
It's so good!
Delicious!
Yum!
Good, good, good, good, good, good, good!
Thank you very much.
Yum! Yum!
I'll have the last one.
Thank you for watching.
Thank you very much for the food.
It was very good.
I'll do my best tomorrow.
It's not every day I get to go to two restaurants in one day.
I'm so glad.
I miss this place so much!
I feel like I've been here before.
I don't know.
I wonder if it's nostalgic.
It feels nostalgic.
I miss it.
I think we're almost there
It seems to be quite really long-establishedIt seems to be a really long-established restaurant.
It's like a gyoza shop in town.
We are here at Aso-ken!
Ta-da!
Here it is!
Did you see it?
You see it, right?
Okay, we're going in.
I'm in, I'm in.
Here we go.
All done.
I want to eat grilled gyoza and sui gyoza.
Making gyoza.
Apparently, sui gyoza is popular too!
Yaki gyoza and sui gyoza, one for each.
And Coca-Cola, please.
That's all.
I'll have a Coke.
Cheers!
We're done.
Yes, sir.
Wrinkles.
How do you make suigyouza?
Boil them?
Do you steam it?
How do you make them?
I've never thought about it.
But I don't think they bake them.
Thank you.
Suigyouza.It's "Suigyoza"!
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
I want to show you something.
It's "suigyouza.
Looks too good!
How do you recommend eating it?
Is that okay?
Please tell me.
Directly.
I see.
You taught me the recommended way to eat it.
Directly like this
With raayu and
and soy sauce
It seems to be recommended to pour it directly on here
It seems to be recommended.
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
All at once!
It's so hot!
It's so good!
Wait, I thought it was the best corn I've ever eaten.
Delicious.
I'm sure you've noticed this restaurant has those chicken wings here too!
Light?
I want some!
chicken wings
I'll call the waiter.
Excuse me, I want some chicken wings!Excuse me, I'd like some chicken wings.
I'll bring you some.
I'd like to order some.
The dumplings are here.
Thank you.
The chicken wings are here, too.
Delicious!
I heard they're famous for their chicken wings too!
Crispy!
They're so delicious!
Yum! Delicious!
So delicious!
Bon appétit!
Yum!
Amazing! There is so much flavor!
Delicious!
Yum!
Tiptoe goodness!
Whoever made this is a genius!
Okay, so
I'm done eating!
It was really delicious!
I'm so happy!
Thank you very much!
Thank you for the food!
I'm going back to my parents' house after this.
Please continue to watch!
I'm at Hakata station right now.
I think my sister and mother are at Hakata station right now. My sister and mother are at Hakata station.
I'm going to meet up with them.
Oh, there they are!
There he is! I found them!
I found them!
To my mother and sister.
Did you cut your bangs?
I did.
You don't like it, do you?
I said no.
It's not too subtle, is it?
What are you gonna do with me?
You're with her, right?
Your sister is the least of our problems.
Whatever.
Do you like it?
I want you to use the first person.
What?
I don't care.
First person, right?
First person, right? - Yeah.
That sucks.
It's not working.
It doesn't work anymore.
We're home.
He's so cute!
Poochie!
We have two dogs.
Mom and sister are having dinner now.My mom and sister are having dinner now.
I just had dumplings.
I'd like to watch over them.
Isn't she cute?
Dinner is ready.
They've prepared a salad and my favorite fruit tart cake!
Thank you very much!
Bon appétit!
You're not a bad person, are you?
Mmm.
Cups.
I really wanted Hiyotan to learn to play the piano.
I really wanted you to learn to play the piano.
When you were little, you played left-handed.
Yes, you were ambidextrous.
I remember.
You could use chopsticks either way.
He could throw away pencils either way.
That was amazing.
Hiyotan was a genius.
Hiyotan was so versatile.
I really think she's a genius.
Hiyotan thought so too.
When I was little?
Grandpa and Mom praised him.
He's going to be a genius in the future.
The thing that really hit home with them was...
The pain will fly away
It was so good for them.
They loved Hiyotan.I loved Hiyotan and the like.
I said, "Ouch, ouch, ouch, it's flying away.
I'd say, "Look, it flew away.
Say bye-bye with all your might
Say bye-bye.
Let's do calisthenics later.
I want to.
I want to do kumite gymnastics later.
I want to do calisthenics later.
Let's play cactus.
I want to play with a fan.
Rock, paper, scissors in the middle.
Hiyotan has the smallest one.
The smallest one is in the middle.
It's not easy being in the middle.
It's harder than being on the side like this.
Sideways is hard, too.
I don't want to do it like this.
I don't want to do it too much because my muscles hurt.
I want to do it, but it hurts.
Like a fan.
Can I do the cactus?
You can do the cactus.
But the cactus hurts.
Why can't I do it?
It's like gymnastics.
You're right.
You might be able to do it.
You don't know your limits.You don't know your limits.
That's enough.
I'm going to take a bath.
Bye bye.
I'm out of the bath.
Wait a minute. I just...
Do you want to try one?
You want to try one?
Okay.
You're an Okinawan. Here.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Okay, here we go.
Let's do it right. Okay.
Ready? Ready?
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Let's do it right one more time.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I'm starting to feel like I'm not supposed to do this.
It's just... it's just... it's just... it's just... it's just...
It looks... it looks really heavy.
Let's go for it.
This is our last year.
Is this what you want?
I know it wasn't easy, but...
It's really...
Laughter.
A little bit.
Laughterlaughter
laughter
Laughter
Ayanan's expression?
Burst of laughter
Ayanan!
Ouch.
Let's go!
I'm running up!
Ready!
Laughing.
I can't do that at all.
I can do it!
It's just a matter of distance.
Let's just really get this over with.
I'm sleepy.
Let's go.
Are you really sleepy under the circumstances?
Laughing.
Let's go!
Ready!
Wait a minute.
What's up?
I think I'll give it to you right away.
I already have to stretch it.
Okay.
That's about right.
Se-Yo!
LOL!
I got it!I got it!
Yes!
LOL!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yes! It worked!
Ha!
Thank you.
Yes, I mean...
The cactus was successful!
Thank you for watching this video of Zagda to the end.
Thank you very much!
Tomorrow is the day of Fukuoka Park.
I will do my best to make you all happy
I will do my best!
Bye bye!